cieaura.com 2013-05-02

# CieAura Privacy Policy | cieaura.com/privacy-policy.html

**A.     PRIVACY POLICY**

Thank you for visiting the Website. We are committed to maintaining the privacy and security of your personally identifiable information as you visit the Website. This Privacy Policy explains our commitment to protect the personally identifiable information we collect, use, or disclose through the Website (this “ **Privacy Policy** ”). Please carefully read this Privacy Policy.

**By visiting our website you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Notice.**

**Overview  
**Any communication or material you provide to us, whether received online, electronically, otherwise collected by or submitted to us, including any data, questions, comments, suggestions or the like is, and will be treated as, non-confidential and non-proprietary. Anything you transmit or post becomes our property and may be used for any purpose, including, but not limited to, reproduction, disclosure, transmission, publication, market, research, development of prospect lists, project planning, broadcast, posting and marketing, among other things.

**Information We Collect  
**Throughout the Website, you may voluntarily submit information that personally identifies you (the “ **Personally Identifiable Information** ”). For example, we may ask you to voluntarily submit Personally Identifiable Information, if you request information regarding our products and services, or request access to certain parts of the Website. Personally Identifiable Information includes, but is not limited to, your (a) name, (b) physical address, (c) phone number, (d) fax number, (e) e-mail address, (f) engine type and value, (g) viewing preferences, and/or (h) product interests and comments. We may maintain a record of this information.

At some sections of the Website, only persons who provide us with the requested information will be able to obtain information or otherwise participate in the Website’s activities, services, and offerings.

To help us tailor the Website to the needs and interests of our visitors, we may collect various types of information from you that do not identify you personally such as the products you purchase, the services you use, the frequency of such purchase and uses, the type of browser you are using (e.g., Firefox, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Windows XP or Mac OS X), the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., Comcast, Earthlink), the length of time you spend on the Website, which pages you visited within the Website, which site you visited before coming to ours, and which site you accessed when you left the Website (collectively, “ **Non-Personally Identifiable Information** ”). “Collected Information” means Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information collectively.

**How We Use the Information We Collect  
**We may use the Personally Identifiable Information (a) to protect and defend our rights or properties, (b) to protect your personal safety and the personal safety of our users and the public in general (whether in emergency situations or otherwise), (c) to provide to third parties to maintain and/or operate the Website, (d) to give to our business partners that provide services selected by you, (e) to fulfill your requests and product or Service orders, (f) to provide you with information on products, specials, newsletters, and other services we provide, (g) for marketing research, (h) to enforce the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy or the Terms of Use, (i) if you are a consultant with the Company, to enforce the terms of your Retailer Agreement and the Policies and Procedures and in connection with our business relationship as set forth in such documents, and (j) as otherwise permitted by law.

We aggregate the Non-Personally Identifiable Information with information collected from other visitors of the Website to track overall visitor traffic patterns. This aggregated information allows us to develop statistics that are helpful to understanding how our visitors use the Website. We use this aggregated information to monitor, maintain, and improve the functionality and content of the Website, making it more responsive to the needs of our visitors. We may also use the Non-Personally Identifiable Information for the enhancement, operation, management or maintenance of the Website, in connection with developing and operating new websites and for historical, statistical, scientific, or other purposes. We reserve the right to use, sell, and assign for any and all purposes all Non-Personally Identifiable Information; and you authorize us to use, sell, and assign, for any and all purposes, all Non-Personally Identifiable Information.

We may provide the Collected Information to our partners, affiliates, subsidiaries, agents and contractors, to a subsequent operator of the Website, or to a successor-in-interest or a purchaser of our business. We may employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Your use of the Website constitutes your consent to the collection and uses of the Collected Information as described in this Privacy Policy.

We may disclose Collected Information in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency’s request or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law.

**Security  
**We place a priority on protecting your Personally Identifiable Information and take commercially reasonable measures to secure and protect such information. However, we cannot guarantee that any electronic commerce is totally secure. For example, we have no control over the information collected by your Internet service provider or your employer (if the Website is made available to you through your employer or if you send us Personally Identifiable Information through your employer-provided email account), or information that you disclose in a public forum. Any such third party that collects your Personally Identifiable Information may use the information in accordance with its terms and conditions of use (and related privacy policies), which may be different from this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for any information collected by such third parties and/or how such information is used or maintained. Neither any third party nor we have the authority to make any representations or commitments on behalf of the other.

**Cookies  
**We reserve the right to place a text file called a “cookie” (or a piece of information transferred to your hard disk for record keeping purposes) or other tracking device in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain information that would personally identify you, although it could enable us to relate your use of the Website to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided to the Website. This may enable us to tailor the Website operation to your needs, likes and dislikes. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can adjust yours to notify you of a cookie placement request, refuse certain cookies or decline cookies completely. We may use third parties to serve our advertisements on other websites. In serving our advertisements, these companies may use cookies and other tracking devices to collect certain information about your visits to other websites (such as browser type), IP address, which page was visited, and time of day). This information may be used to evaluate our online advertising campaigns or to tailor promotions and other marketing messages to you. You may elect to refuse cookies. Please refer to your browser Help instructions to learn more about cookies and how to manage their use.

**Collection of Information by Third Party Sites  
**The Website may contain links to other Internet sites. These other sites may have different privacy policies and this Privacy Policy does not apply to such other sites. We are not responsible for the data policies or procedures or the content of these linked websites.

**Unsubscribing and Opting-Out  
**If you have opted-in to receive status updates regarding our products or Services, you may opt-out, at any time, from receiving any such status update by selecting the appropriate option on the informational page for such product or service located on the Website.

**Access  
**We will maintain procedures consistent with applicable law for you to gain access to your Personally Identifiable Information and, when appropriate, correct, change, or delete any such Personally Identifiable Information.

**Children’s Policy  
**The Website is not intended for use by children. Children under the age of 18 are not authorized to use the Website and should not submit any personal information to us. We do not knowingly market to or solicit information from children.

**Business Transactions**  
We reserve the right to transfer any and all information that we collect from visitors, or that we otherwise collect concerning or in connection with the Website, including Collected Information, to a third party in the event of a sale or other transfer of assets or of any portion of our business. In the event we enter a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your Collected Information may be among the assets transferred.

**Changes to the Policy**  
We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time without specific notice to you. The most recent form of this Privacy Policy will be posted at all times on the Website, and you should review this Privacy Policy each time upon visiting or using the Website. You agree that each time you enter or use the Website, you accept and comply with, and agree to be bound by, this Privacy Policy, as modified.

If you do not agree to any provision of this Privacy Policy, or to any modification to this policy, please do not use the Website.

**Questions, Comments, or Complaints Regarding this Privacy Policy**  
If you are aware of any violations of this Privacy Policy or if you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at 7251 West Lake Mead Boulevard, Suite 300 Las Vegas, NV 89128.

By using the Website you acknowledge acceptance of this Privacy Policy in effect at the time of use. This Privacy Policy was last revised on September 21, 2010.

Copyright © 2010 CieAura, LLC. All rights reserved.
